

# ROY MIZRAHI

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

### **PROFILE**

Shai Cohen has experience working as a React.js developer.

In-depth knowledge of JavaScript, CSS, HTML, and front-end languages. Knowledge of React tools including React.js, Webpack, Enzyme, Redux, and Flux.

Experience with user interface design. Experience with browser-based debugging and performance testing software. Excellent troubleshooting skills. Good project management skills. Collaborates closely with product managers, designers, and other engineering teams.

## **EDUCATION**

(HIT)

B.sc. In Computer Science Holon Institutue of Technology(HIT) 2008 - 2012

- I have studied basic software technology subjects like DS, Algorithms, DBMS, OS, CA, AI etc.
- Apart from this, I have done courses on Deep Learning, Data Science, Cloud Computing and Full Stack Development.

### Computers ORT College

Practical Engineering in computers ORT College 2004 - 2008

- I have studied basic software engineering subjects like DS, Algorithms, DBMS, OS, CA, AI etc.
- I was selected for Merit cum Means Scholarship which is given to top 10% of students in college. I have received award from respected director for consistently best performance in academics.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### VYYO Inc.

Data Analyst

January 2010 - December 2013

- Developed and automated component databases using VBA, facilitating digitalization and analysis.
- Contributed to the digitalization of document transfer processes.

#### Motorola Inc.

Data Analyst Programmer January 2014–October 2017

- Designed, developed, and automated analytical tools and HR/budgeting systems for Motorola offices worldwide.
- Utilized VB and SQL Server to create interfaces supporting offices in Europe, Asia, USA, South America, and Israel.

#### Bank Leumi.

Full Stack C#/ASP.NET Developer November 2019 –

 Architecture, development, upgrade, and maintenance of Variety of capital market systems (.NET) for the large variety of branches and strategic data analysis including: Development of web pages and services using ASP.NET, JS, C#, REST API and SOAP API.

Leveraging ETL processes utilizing SSIS, C#, CMD, PowerShell, BASH, and REST API to efficiently retrieve and integrate critical market data from big data contributors, ensuring accurate and timely insights for strategic analysis and decision-making..